(Leonard:)Okay, that's all I got.
(Leonard:)Howard, you're up.
(Howard:)Um... tell us about your work, Amy.
(Amy:)I doubt you'd understand.
(Amy:)Sheldon tells me you only
have a master's degree.
(Howard:)Raj, do you have any
questions for Amy?
(Amy:)I'm curious as to why
we're not eating alone.
(Sheldon:)They can't function without me.
(Sheldon:)I'm the social glue that holds
this little group together.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Leonard:)Listen, can I talk to you
about your girlfriend?
(Sheldon:)She's not my girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)She's a girl and she's my friend,
(Sheldon:)but there's no touching or
unsanitary exchange of saliva.
(Penny:)Got it.
(Sheldon:)Although, for the record,
on one occasion,
(Sheldon:)she licked her thumb to
remove raspberry jelly
(Sheldon:)from the corner of my mouth.
(Sheldon:)It's an action we both
regret to this day.
(Leonard:)Uh-huh.